hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft it is
time for demise dares i've got rendog
here who has registered some interest
because he has absolutely no diamonds
he's actually waiting for me there i've
made a couple of alterations i've made
it minus 65 why in the void i did a bit
more research and you can actually get
that far without taking damage but soon
after that you do
i've made the tube a little bit taller
and i've extended this a couple of
blocks other than that everything else
is the same
and the diamonds are still ready to be
won
but look what
what are they doing seriously
seriously
right next to it when we're trying to do
demise dares they don't even do they see
me oh that's creep oh that's really
creepy
they they're absolutely following
it's like the eyes of the painting
they're following me
yeah i see you uh
you see those guys ren
yes they're
i think they're just the audience
right
if they if they're not gonna hurt us i
don't think we should hurt them
this is really weird they're just not
moving at all yep this has definitely
lowered my chances of getting through
this alive okay so you want to make some
diamonds
yeah i'm pretty poor right now man
you're paying for sahara membership
demise was pretty expensive and logs
aren't really selling so
two of those are my
well yeah you can get some diamonds back
my friend by putting it all on the line
so
do you know what this is about or do you
need to explain a little bit um i've
literally just got here i know that
there is death involved though so i'm
supposed to undermine somebody i have
proven that all of these dares are
possible to do without dying
right basically i'm gonna hit this
button and that will shoot a bit of
paper that will give you a dare and then
i will say i dare you to
and then if you do it you okay i don't
mean to alarm you though but we got
problems
they decided that they wanted to fight
that scared the life out of me i will
not be the first to die so you're not
getting any help from me good luck no no
no come on get out of get the life out
of me they were waiting
okay so the infestation has been cleared
and you're gonna dare me to do stuff and
i could die if i do it is that hard you
could die yes that's um kind of the
point but i have faith in you and that's
why there's lots of diamonds on the line
every day you complete you get 50
diamonds
whoa okay well now we're cooking with
gas my dude all right now we're talking
i mean look put diamonds in front of me
i'll probably do anything so
yeah you ready for your first dare
i think so
yes
all right what is the totem
catch the totem catch the totem right
let's set this one up so
basically i'm going to make a tower
you should start making your way up to
the top because that's where you're
going to be i would it doesn't matter if
you uh take your stuff off or not
because you'll be able to collect it so
when you reach the top
i'm going to ask you to throw the totem
onto the ground towards me okay right
and i'm going to count one two jump
you'll then have you have to jump and
catch the totem before you hit the
ground
right the totem if you catch it will
save you if you don't put it in the
right slot or you don't catch it splat
goes the red dog
okay um
when you pick up an item in minecraft
does it go straight into your hot bar i
don't know
good luck
[Laughter]
you gotta throw the totem towards me and
then i will count one i'll count throw
one two jump okay
have you tasted this
yes i did it myself
all right okay okay and all of these
myself to prove that i'm not trying to
scam anyone okay so i've got to say this
are you ready ren yeah i dare you
to jump off the scaffolding and throw
the totem are you ready for it
no but
50 diamonds throw
one two
jump no no no no no no you needed to
like scaffolding oh jesus oh
he did it
what the heck i forgot you needed elytra
oh man
yeah baby you you must have collected
that
second yeah before it hit the ground yep
mm-hmm
so about those 50 diamonds uh yeah yeah
you did it i mean next time i gotta
remember that you need a lighter for
this this is meant to be a flying
challenge but all right
50 diamonds to to the red dog
he's sweet
okay lucky man all right oh man that
feels so good you've got you've got the
option now um you can do another dare if
you want or we can you can just walk
away with your diamonds oh
okay well do i get to know what the
dares are first or press the button you
press the button and that's it yeah you
get you get okay um
do you want to risk all right because
you've already made back your demise
diamonds that's right i need to make
back my uh my sahara now diamonds so
risk it for the biscuit baby let's do it
okay
exit the aquarium oh okay so
you're not allowed to use any tools in
this one you're not allowed any helmet
or uh armor on this one so pop that in
the chest over here the goal of this one
you've got to jump in the aquarium and
you've got to work your way out you've
got to punch your way out of the top if
you get out the top without drowning you
win
okay um now just to just to check you
have tested this right i did it yep it
works
okay great
um i'm not the greatest swimmer so this
should be interesting all right i gotta
say the words red dog i dare you to
escape the aquarium
okay go i take the dare let's go baby
yes come on come on
punch your little hand faster you stupid
little minecraft didn't it no dude i'm
running out of bubbles
what's going on
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
that was the best thing i've ever seen
that's not how i expected that to go
why
it was why
[Music]
why
my stomach hurts dude
i'm quitting hermitcraft thanks for
watching everybody
red you've got to put on the skin i'm so
sorry
you've completed the challenge
green feeling dead has never felt so bad
dude
this is this is awful everyone's gonna
know when you press tab you can see that
you're all grayed out
yeah
i was supposed to be undermisible dude i
spent like three days making myself
under my support
you failed on the one that's the easiest
to win
why
okay well at least i made 50 diamonds
um i feel you know what actually i i
feel like something needs to be done
about this korean okay i've i'm i need
to bury myself right now six feet under
thanks for the 50 diamonds dude um
you know before you go uh yeah no hard
feelings right
no no hard feelings
right yeah
revenge is not in all the game it's just
a part of the game yeah i hope you die i
i hope you die i i mean
the zombie korean all right bye ryan
that was
amazing okay so i've had two other
people that have been interested in
doing demise dares but here's the thing
everyone that dies in this little mini
game they're gonna be after me so
i i don't want too many people so i
might only
do one more i think i could handle two
people after me but three that's a no-go
so
let's move ren his little face
over to the brand new
dead team
there we go
ren
you are the first to go
but don't worry because you won't be the
last now that someone is on the dead
team
i'm sure ren will be going after
everyone else that's still alive
but i think he's going to focus
on the person that deaded him although i
would argue
personally i would argue that ren deaded
himself
because this is actually the easiest one
to get out of because all you gotta do
even if you went in here and just
crouched i can get back all of my
bubbles
and then even if i was punching my way
out i could do it like
the aquarium one was such an easy one
but he just somehow overshot
i didn't expect for a second that that's
how that would go down but i think we
can definitely call this
the beginning of the demise
so i'll replenish all of these
dispensers
and the next person that actually
messaged me was stress monster and if we
all know stress which we we do
um i have a feeling that she might panic
a little bit
on all of these
and it'll be really funny to see if she
makes it through this has been diamonds
well spent in my opinion so while we
wait for stress let's head on back to
the bunker and do a little bit of work
there so let's hop down into here i've
still got a very big blank slate to work
with and i'll be honest i'm still not
entirely sure what to do but what i'm
thinking is a modern
style cave that is also a bunker so
that's gonna that sounds a little bit
confusing but you know the poultry man
cave not that i know what the portrait
man cave looks like it's it's like a big
cave like a modern james bond thing
that's basically what i'm thinking i'm
gonna go for
so in order to do that
we need to take a look at this space and
try and picture
what the end result will be
and for that
i need to lay down some foundations
so the cave shape will have to be
irregular because we kind of want it to
look
kind of natural
working underground is is actually
not a lot of fun i've got to admit it's
not a lot of fun especially when you've
got to build up the top there but if we
make
some kind of cave shape here we can have
some underground waterfalls we can have
a building and then that gives us plenty
to work with in terms of hiding stuff
and traps
so
let's kick this off with a bit of a time
lapse shall we
building underground always means that
you're restricted by space so it's
probably going to be a couple times that
i'm going to have to expand the area but
i'm pretty happy with the size that it
is now and i want to make this feel like
a proper cave bunker so i started by
making the walls out of stone and cobble
but then i quickly realized i don't
really know what i want to make on the
other side so i kind of started some and
then i ran out of concrete but i think
this looks pretty cool i think this is
actually going pretty well but i'm going
to slow down a little bit one because
i've run out of white concrete and i
want to make sure that i do a lot of the
structure before i finish every part of
the cave and two it's actually getting a
little bit dangerous now because i
haven't lit it up
there's there's been a couple of very
close calls next to a creeper and i'm
too scared to test if a creeper it will
actually get through my arm i don't know
if i'm creeper proof is what i'm saying
and i don't want to find out the hard
way either
okay so i really really like this
entrance that i've made it just it feels
perfect it it sort of takes you down
into
the k setting which i think has actually
gone quite well like the mixture of the
cobblestone and the stone the way it
goes into the walls and sometimes
protrudes out that's awesome and i'm
pretty sure that's where i want to go
but the second half all of that bit
there is going to be a mixture of
concrete and glass and yeah it's getting
it's getting dangerous i need more light
stress monster has messaged me on
discord and asked if she can do some
demise dares so what we're gonna do is
head back to the mini game district and
something has appeared in the shopping
district it looks like a giant hourglass
full of diamond blocks
it makes it makes our diamond blocks
look pretty pathetic that is massive it
looks like it's actually acting like
sand like it's falling
so there's some sort of countdown with a
redstone thing is that wait is that
cherry
is that something to do is that the same
logo as this one thing over here
oh
oh it's closed cherry is closed for
refurbishment
oh dude that's totally the cherry i
tried to go in when it was closed
that is totally the cherry logo so
something's going on over there and it's
not worth risking your life for a couple
of phantoms so let's go over to the mini
game district hi stress
hi
did you want to do some dares for cash
money diamonds i i saw this chest
alright and i have to say i am very very
very very very skinned i have no
diamonds at all and this yes is very
very very tempting
oh god
what is it exit the aquarium
oh no
so this is really simple
okay what to do
is run in and escape the aquarium out
the top
out the top yeah at the top
yep so you got it right i have to okay
run in and escape so that's it so right
i'm gonna say the words i dare you and
then you're off okay
so do i okay i i break it okay yeah i'm
gonna break the top right ready three
two one stress i dare you to exit the
aquarium go all right i'm off i'm off
i'm off
oh no
come on stress it sucks me in
oh i'm doing it quinn
i'm gonna die and i
oh my god what is this
hang on
i'm not even dying what's going on
how have you done this wait
i'm a pro agreeant don't go judging me
right now
oh my god
i don't know how you did that with the
bubbles
i told you okay i'm a pro and when
diamonds are on the line i can do these
you just broke the rules of minecraft
how does that make sense there's bubbles
there
heyon didn't you just say that you did
all of these yeah yeah but i did it
properly i didn't break the rules
the rules of mine well you did it okay
fine all right
i mean that's that's cool you just you
just break physics that's cool you take
take your 50 diamonds i i want my 50
diamonds green i heard that since that
was so easy do you want to do another
dare
oh do you know what i've won me 50. i
think yeah i think i want to do another
day oh i thought you were going to cash
out okay you ready
no i ain't one of those people yeah go
for it oh no
okay
you've got to oh
have you got an elytra
yeah all right grab your elytra
and some rockets we gotta go somewhere
your dare is to reach minus 65 in the
void
so you got to press f3
yeah jump down you got to you got to fly
and it's up to you how you want to do
this
you can sink down or you can just fall
like this you reach -65 and then you
gotta fly back up so f3 will be your
friend and i i can't actually tell if
you reach minus 65 but all right
for it i won't lie i can obviously see
in the in the footage so
stress i dare you to jump in the void
off you go oh i'm so scared okay
oh my god i'm gonna do what you did you
yeah okay
oh
minus 65 minus six five i'm doing it
green
i'm doing it
all right all right all right all right
it's nearly there
um
you made it
i didn't agree you did it
could you actually believe that i just
did that how many hearts did you have
i have i think it was like four and a
half oh god oh
no
congratulations i nearly died
are you
are you as surprised as i am right now
no i had complete faith in you you're
you're a hundred diamonds up
i'm a hundred diamonds up everyone yeah
so are you gonna cash out now or do you
want to do another dare oh
do you should i do another day do you
want me to do no
you could do you could do as many dares
as you like
oh i feel like i have to
okay so one more dare
yes yes okay
oh i got it i've got it what does it say
it says fire fly through the tube okay
right so this one's a another flying
challenge
all you gotta do
is fly straight through oh no this white
tube no this is where i'm gonna fail
well you've committed already
oh no
i can't i can't fly through tunnels
stressed i dare you to fly through the
tube
go
oh this is gonna be embarrassing i'm not
even gonna hit the entrance i swear
right hang on okay okay oh oh oh oh
you did it
i did it
oh you've got 150 there's only one dare
left do you want to do you want to do
the dare
i'm
oh no right you need your elixir and
nothing else again for this one stress
monster
yes i dare you
to catch the totem mid-air
okay three all right two one throw throw
one two jump
oh no where is it oh it's already on the
floor no
i had no chance with that one
you did you didn't even go to the totem
either
[Laughter]
i'm so sorry
yeah you've got to change your skin
no
i you should have you should have cashed
out
well i don't keep any of those diamonds
now yeah you get 150 diamonds but you've
lost the game of demise
[Laughter]
can you tell that i'm like oh my god the
diamonds i lose the time
you only care about one thing i only
care about one thing oh no that sucks
but you still you're still a hundred
diamonds up because it comes with 50
right yeah well you cost you it cost you
50 to be in the game of demise oh it did
you're right okay yes so i'm 100
diamonds up
well well done but you've got to change
your skin
yeah thank you it is kind of halloweeny
and half dead but yeah i get it i gotta
change it
no hard feelings right no never you
you've made me rich i'm a happy bunny
so that went i i thought she was gonna
clear me out of diamonds
no sir
stress is now on team dead and it could
be
i'm gonna have to close this down
honestly this this thing is great
because i've actually got x here
exercise
void who wants to actually do a demise
dare as well so this could mean that
three people okay so after this we're
closing down the shop people are making
too much money from me do you have any
idea how much diamonds i've spent
already
look that was a full stack it's now
under half
i am wasting diamonds okay so let's get
x and see if he wants to do a dare
hello good sir
hi he got in contact with me saying that
you've picked out a debt i mean normally
it's my job to press the button but you
went ahead and did it anyway that's cool
that's cool i i was so excited i just i
you know i saw these diamonds and i was
like oh i got to get involved in this
well which dare did you get
i got the void jump
you know and that gives me a good
feeling because void is in my name for
this dare we need to head over to the
end and it's it's basically yeah what it
says on the tin should we go
i
let's do it all i need you to do for
this day i'm going to say the words x
jump in the void now you have to
actually press f3
and you have to hit
minus 65 on the y coordinate minus 65. i
promise at minus 65 you don't take
damage but it's pretty close to the
limit all right yeah well you're not
allowed a totem of undying that is that
is
oh oh okay no no
now i'm on edge
now i'm on edge oh geez okay
all right so uh when i say the word this
is it i'll i'll dare you to do it and
then i'll tell you to go are you ready
yeah my heart's founding a little bit
remember there's 50 diamonds on the line
so
x i dare you to jump in the void go
oh
okay
oh you should have gone straight down
oh no
oh my god one heart one heart
don't die from fall damage now
oh i saw you taking damage
oh
okay well done
i thought that was easy but that was
terrifying
that was literally terrifying all right
let's head back to the to the demise
dares area then well done okay so
there's your 50 diamonds for doing doing
the dare uh do you think you can
actually do more than one if you want do
you want to do some
think so i think that was an easy 50
diamonds you know
miniature heart attack though you're
actually cashing out
i'm cashing out yeah
well if you actually if you turn around
look at the alive and dead team
two other hermits just did the dares and
they pushed it so i salute you for
cashing out because they didn't and they
paid the price oh man did they even get
any diamonds then yes dress got 150
diamonds and ren got 50 diamonds wow
you're rich
i'm not rich this is me closing up
demise dares because i'm i'm not wasting
any more diamonds on this i've done that
closed we're closed for business people
are bleeding me dry here
no more device dares
wow i'm glad i cashed out when i did
so that is everything for today's
episode what an episode two people have
demised ren and stress fell for our
demise dares we lost uh a lot of
diamonds hundreds of diamonds
and xo xi zuma also did the dubai stairs
and survived and at the same time we
have done some
pretty good progress to our bunker
hidden underneath here but we're gonna
need isko for a bit more help on getting
this done and i've also heard that mumbo
jumbo has started his own bunker he
started his own bunker
without without us don't worry i see
this guy in the background why has he
got a pumpkin on
someone needs to tell mumbo
to come to the meetings
well thank you very much for watching i
hope you enjoyed today's episode and
i'll see you in the next one good bye